Have your photo taken
写真を撮ってもらって
May I?
いい ですか?
I'm sleepy though.
眠 い けど
Yeah, I'm sleepy.
うん、 眠い
sleepy?
眠い?
Yeah.
うん
Were you nervous?
緊張した?
Yeah.
うん
sleepy?
眠い?
Yeah.
うん
sleepy?
眠い?
feelings
気 持
Bad?
ち 悪い?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah, show me.
うん、見せて
Are you doing that?
お客それしてんの?
That's really great.
ちゃんと偉いね
Yeah.
うん
Hey, look.
ねえ、ほら
What are your eyes?
何そのお目
Get off your ass, you son of a bitch.
お尻はやめろ、この野郎みたいな
Is that what it feels like?
そんな感じ?
Well then, I'll leave it to you for a while.
じゃあ、ちょっとおまく
ERROR
お尻に引く引く
Please spread it out.
広げててね
Yes, a present.
はい、プレゼント
It's lingering.
じりじりしてて
Yeah.
うん
It's already wet.
もう濡れてきたじゃん
It's getting wet.
濡れてきたじゃん
Look.
ほら
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Ah, this.
あー、これ
copper?
どう?
This is dangerous, right?
これ、やばいでしょ?
He's a bad guy.
やばいやつだよ
The shape is amazing.
形がすごいんだよ
How far can it go?
どこまで入る?
Is this okay?
これ大丈夫?
Can you fit more?
もっと入る?
this.
これ
to this point?
ここまで?
picture?
え?
Why don't you come in more?
もっと入んないの?
Is there anything standing there?
なにか立ってる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
So, do you want to get it wet?
じゃあ、濡らすの?
Are you going to get this wet?
これ、濡らすの?
Then there's the pussy.
そしたら、おまんこ
It'll come in.
入るよね
You did it yourself, right?
自分でやったでしょ
Yes, lick it.
そう、舐めてて
Lick it again.
もう一回舐めて
Kabi no Rildo.
カビのリルド
Okay, lick it.
いいよ、舐めて
So bad.
すげーやばい
What a bastard.
す げ ー 野 郎 だ
Look here.
こっち見て
It's really in there.
すげー入ってるよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
I think I should sleep.
寝てしようかな
This time.
このタイム
There's a lot in it.
すごく入ってるよ
I was sleeping
寝てた
law.
ほ う
sleeping
寝
Tetaho.
て たほう
I should have slept.
寝てたほう
Shall we go to bed?
ベッド行く?
I'll go there soon.
もうちょい、そっち行くね
Please stand this up.
これ、ひでやっぱ立てて
this?
これ?
here?
ここ?
Let's put it in.
入れちゃおう
Just put it in.
そのまま入れよ